<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>News Archives - X93C Ndcs Undp</title>
	<atom:link href="https://x93c.ndcs.undp.org/category/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://x93c.ndcs.undp.org/category/news/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 08:36:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Inter Miami is building team to win US Open this year</title>
		<link>https://x93c.ndcs.undp.org/inter-miami-is-building-team-to-win-us-open-this-year/</link>
					<comments>https://x93c.ndcs.undp.org/inter-miami-is-building-team-to-win-us-open-this-year/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 08:35:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://x93c.ndcs.undp.org/?p=126</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Inter Miami is building team to win US Open this year Inter Miami’s hopes of qualifying for the Major League Soccer playoffs look extremely bleak. After all, the club has the second-worst record in the entire league and the fewest points in the Eastern Conference. Miami is currently nine points away from Montreal for the ... <a title="Inter Miami is building team to win US Open this year" class="read-more" href="https://x93c.ndcs.undp.org/inter-miami-is-building-team-to-win-us-open-this-year/" aria-label="More on Inter Miami is building team to win US Open this year">Read more</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://x93c.ndcs.undp.org/inter-miami-is-building-team-to-win-us-open-this-year/">Inter Miami is building team to win US Open this year</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://x93c.ndcs.undp.org">X93C Ndcs Undp</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Inter Miami is building team to win US Open this year</p>



<p>Inter Miami’s hopes of qualifying for the Major League Soccer playoffs look extremely bleak. After all, the club has the second-worst record in the entire league and the fewest points in the Eastern Conference. Miami is currently nine points away from Montreal for the final wild-card spot in the standings. While the team is way behind in the playoff race, there is another way for them to collect a trophy.</p>



<p>Miami is currently a semifinalist for the U.S. Open Cup. Despite their league struggles, the club has navigated its way through the knockout competition to the final four. Inter has advanced through the competition after beating USL Championship sides Miami FC, the Charleston Battery and the Birmingham Legion, as well as fellow top-flight team Nashville. The Floridian club is now adding some series talent to their squad ahead of a semifinal matchup with Cincinnati.</p>



<p>Busquets, Alba reuniting with Messi in Miami</p>



<p>Lionel Messi grabbed headlines when he chose Inter Miami over a more lucrative deal with Saudi Arabia side Al-Hilal. The Argentine superstar will undoubtedly be the most impressive player to ever play Stateside in MLS. Despite being in the autumn of his career, Messi still racked up impressive numbers last season with Paris Saint-Germain. The playmaker picked up 41 combined goals and assists in the same amount of total matches.</p>



<p>Along with Messi, Sergio Busquets has also joined his former teammate on South Beach. Much like Messi, the defensive midfielder rejected a massive Saudi offer to join Miami as well. The duo previously spent 13 seasons together at Barcelona before Messi departed for Paris. Busquets, however, will not be the only former teammate to be reunited with the Argentina international Stateside.</p>



<p>Jordi Alba is also nearing a deal to join Miami as well. The defender departs Barca after 11 seasons with the Catalan club. To help make room for Alba, Miami is reportedly set to trade Rodolfo Pizarro to LA Galaxy. The former Barca trio collected five LaLiga titles together in Spain.</p>



<p>Inter Miami has ample time before US Open Cup semis<br>Messi and company should have plenty of time to prepare for an Inter Miami US Open Cup match. The semifinal stage of the tournament does not take place until August 23rd. All three players should be in full swing ahead of the matchup with Cincinnati. The winner of this fixture will go on to face either Houston or Real Salt Lake for the trophy. Although this trophy can’t compare to a La Liga or a Champions League, an Inter Miami US Open win would mean the world to the franchise.</p>



<p>PHOTO: IMAGO &amp; Icon Sportswire</p>



<p>Guide to Major League Soccer<br>Here are some resources to help you get the most out of MLS Season Pass!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://x93c.ndcs.undp.org/inter-miami-is-building-team-to-win-us-open-this-year/">Inter Miami is building team to win US Open this year</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://x93c.ndcs.undp.org">X93C Ndcs Undp</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://x93c.ndcs.undp.org/inter-miami-is-building-team-to-win-us-open-this-year/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A diverse U.S. squad heads to women’s World Cup</title>
		<link>https://x93c.ndcs.undp.org/a-diverse-u-s-squad-heads-to-womens-world-cup/</link>
					<comments>https://x93c.ndcs.undp.org/a-diverse-u-s-squad-heads-to-womens-world-cup/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 08:33:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://x93c.ndcs.undp.org/?p=123</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A diverse U.S. squad heads to women’s World Cup Trinity Rodman will make her World Cup debut alongside veteran defender Crystal Dunn on a team that features seven Black players. A new era is dawning for the U.S. women’s national soccer team, as the most diverse squad the program has ever produced will pursue an ... <a title="A diverse U.S. squad heads to women’s World Cup" class="read-more" href="https://x93c.ndcs.undp.org/a-diverse-u-s-squad-heads-to-womens-world-cup/" aria-label="More on A diverse U.S. squad heads to women’s World Cup">Read more</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://x93c.ndcs.undp.org/a-diverse-u-s-squad-heads-to-womens-world-cup/">A diverse U.S. squad heads to women’s World Cup</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://x93c.ndcs.undp.org">X93C Ndcs Undp</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>A diverse U.S. squad heads to women’s World Cup</p>



<p>Trinity Rodman will make her World Cup debut alongside veteran defender Crystal Dunn on a team that features seven Black players.</p>



<p>A new era is dawning for the U.S. women’s national soccer team, as the most diverse squad the program has ever produced will pursue an unprecedented third consecutive title when the World Cup kicks off this month in Australia and New Zealand.</p>



<p>The squad represents a major shift from its early days and even more recent USA teams that were overwhelmingly white. Trinity Rodman will make her World Cup debut alongside veteran defender Crystal Dunn on a team that features seven Black players.</p>



<p>“The issue is partly about economics and partly about how hard it is to eliminate stereotypes people have about who can succeed at what sports,” said Jon Solomon, editorial director of the Aspen Institute Sports &amp; Society Program.</p>



<p>Retired USA goalkeeper Briana Scurry said, “for decades I was the only one of color on the roster that started.”</p>



<p>“(Now) you have players that are really making inroads and making impacts and impressions in more ways than one who are going to be there a long time because they’re very young,” she told Reuters.</p>



<p>Scurry’s penalty kick save in front of 90,185 fans at the Rose Bowl in Pasadena, California, helped the United States win the 1999 Cup, turning the team into idols for millions of American girls, in what was seen as a turning point for women’s sports.</p>



<p>That squad offered little representation for girls of color. Scurry said she struggled to secure endorsement deals after her heroics, as the only openly gay player and as a Black woman.</p>



<p>“I was always going to be authentically me. I never hid that I was gay. I just was being who I am,” said Scurry, a Hall of Famer and the host of the “Counterattack” podcast.</p>



<p>Scurry now sees the diverse soccer landscape she had wanted to be part of, and feels gratified that her pursuit likely provided some inspiration. “It’s awesome because now other young girls think that they can, too.”</p>



<p>Dunn helped the United States to its fourth overall title in 2019, but said last month she struggled growing up to feel she belonged.</p>



<p>“It hasn’t been the easiest road, obviously,” Dunn told reporters. “There are moments where I felt like I needed to conform to the environment and say, ‘Okay, let me tone down who I am because I feel like there’s very few of us on this team.’”</p>



<p>Dunn was often the only Black starter for her country in the 2019 World Cup, then celebrated as the most diverse U.S. women’s squad.</p>



<p>“There’s so many more great young players out there that are more of a better mixture of what this country is,” said Scurry. “This country isn’t just white.”</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Children&#8217;s exposure to soccer is often where inequality begins</h2>



<p>The increased diversity at the highest level of women’s U.S. soccer coincides with a multi-year effort to get more minority kids onto the pitch.</p>



<p>“It’s often difficult and takes time to widen the demographic pool of young players,” said Aspen Institute’s Solomon.</p>



<p>The institute’s most recent survey found that 39% of Hispanic and 20% of white students had played soccer in high school versus only 10% of Black students.</p>



<p>A U.S. Soccer Foundation survey in 2008 found that even as the game experienced tremendous national growth at the youth level, large swathes of the country were being left behind.</p>



<p>“We developed a strategy and a business plan that focused and made a priority of increasing access and opportunity for underrepresented populations, particularly children in underserved, underrepresented communities,” U.S. Soccer Foundation CEO Ed Foster-Simeon said in an interview.</p>



<p>The foundation has provided more than half a million children from “under-resourced” communities with free programs, building more than 600 “mini-pitches” designed for the youth game across the country.</p>



<p>While minority participation has improved “quite a bit,” Foster-Simeon said, “it’s nowhere near where we want it to be.”</p>



<p>The problem has not been limited to soccer.</p>



<p>Girls at predominantly white high schools typically see 82% of the athletic opportunities boys do, according to a Women’s Sports Foundation (WSF) report last year. That figure falls to 67% in schools where students of color are the majority.</p>



<p>Girls of color are “short-changed” in school and club programs, said WSF research head Karen Issokson-Silver.</p>



<p>“Sport is a microcosm of society, so a lot of the things that we see in society, whether that’s systemic racism or archaic gender norms &#8230; then you are likely to see them in sport,” she said.</p>



<p>WSF’s Sports 4 Life program, founded nine years ago in conjunction with espnW — the cable network’s women’s sports branch — works to increase participation for girls of color.</p>



<p>The chance to see a World Cup team with many diverse players will play a part for the next generation, said Issokson-Silver.</p>



<p>“When it comes to girls having an opportunity to see what’s possible for themselves, that kind of visibility, whether it’s a high school level, the collegiate level or&#8230; at the elite levels of play is monumental,” she said.</p>



<p>That message is not lost on the women of the 2023 U.S. national team.</p>



<p>“Growing up, I don’t really feel like that was something that I saw in professional soccer and on national teams,” 23-year-old defender Naomi Girma, who will make her World Cup debut, told reporters. “I feel honored to be that representation.”</p>



<p>At a media event last month, Dunn noted that even things like finding hair and makeup stylists who work with Black women for team events can be a challenge.</p>



<p>She hopes to leave the sport in a place where those that follow “don’t have to fight for the same things.”</p>



<p>“I can’t hide that I’m a Black woman,” said Dunn. “And so I think for me, just the more that I step into that space and I own it has really allowed and given other women of color the green light.”</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://x93c.ndcs.undp.org/a-diverse-u-s-squad-heads-to-womens-world-cup/">A diverse U.S. squad heads to women’s World Cup</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://x93c.ndcs.undp.org">X93C Ndcs Undp</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://x93c.ndcs.undp.org/a-diverse-u-s-squad-heads-to-womens-world-cup/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Soccer players and fans left perplexed after ball crosses the line … but no goal is awarded</title>
		<link>https://x93c.ndcs.undp.org/soccer-players-and-fans-left-perplexed-after-ball-crosses-the-line-but-no-goal-is-awarded/</link>
					<comments>https://x93c.ndcs.undp.org/soccer-players-and-fans-left-perplexed-after-ball-crosses-the-line-but-no-goal-is-awarded/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 08:31:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://x93c.ndcs.undp.org/?p=120</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Soccer players and fans left perplexed after ball crosses the line … but no goal is awarded Soccer players and fans were left dumbfounded after a referee and his officials failed to award a goal after the ball crossed the line by about half a meter. Inside the opening 10 seconds of Colo-Colo’s Chilean Cup ... <a title="Soccer players and fans left perplexed after ball crosses the line … but no goal is awarded" class="read-more" href="https://x93c.ndcs.undp.org/soccer-players-and-fans-left-perplexed-after-ball-crosses-the-line-but-no-goal-is-awarded/" aria-label="More on Soccer players and fans left perplexed after ball crosses the line … but no goal is awarded">Read more</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://x93c.ndcs.undp.org/soccer-players-and-fans-left-perplexed-after-ball-crosses-the-line-but-no-goal-is-awarded/">Soccer players and fans left perplexed after ball crosses the line … but no goal is awarded</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://x93c.ndcs.undp.org">X93C Ndcs Undp</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Soccer players and fans left perplexed after ball crosses the line … but no goal is awarded</p>



<p>Soccer players and fans were left dumbfounded after a referee and his officials failed to award a goal after the ball crossed the line by about half a meter.</p>



<p>Inside the opening 10 seconds of Colo-Colo’s Chilean Cup match against Unión La Calera, Colo-Colo defender Alan Saldivia played a wayward pass back to goalkeeper Fernando de Paul.</p>



<p>As the ball made its way towards the goal, de Paul tried desperately to get back and prevent it from going over the line – but he failed to get there in time and kicked the ball away after it had gone over the line.</p>



<p>Some of La Calera’s players began celebrating, but quickly stopped when they realized referee Víctor Abarzúa hadn’t signaled for a goal and Colo-Colo continued playing.</p>



<p>To make matters worse, before La Calera could even make its case to the officials, Colo-Colo went up the other end and immediately scored to make it 1-0.</p>



<p>Adding insult to injury, Colo-Colo went on to win the match 6-1 and reach the regional semifinals, while La Calera finished the match with 10 men.</p>



<p>Some of Chile’s stadiums do have video assistant refereeing (VAR) – including the Estadio Monumental where this match was played – but it isn’t used during the earlier rounds of the Chilean Cup.</p>



<p>Roberto Tobar, the head of Chile’s refereeing committee, put the error down to a lack of concentration from the referee and his assistants.</p>



<p>“Regrettably … a quite obvious error was committed by the refereeing team in not sanctioning a legitimate goal for Unión La Calera after an own goal by a defender of Colo-Colo,” he said, according to outlet La Tercera.</p>



<p>“This type of situation, which very rarely occurs within 10 seconds of the start of a match, means that the referees are not 100% activated and, as a result, are not in an appropriate position to make the best decision.</p>



<p>“Situations that are unexpected are when concentration and a good location take precedence to make a very good decision,” Tobar added.</p>



<p>It’s unlikely that explanation will make La Calera fans feel any better.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://x93c.ndcs.undp.org/soccer-players-and-fans-left-perplexed-after-ball-crosses-the-line-but-no-goal-is-awarded/">Soccer players and fans left perplexed after ball crosses the line … but no goal is awarded</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://x93c.ndcs.undp.org">X93C Ndcs Undp</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://x93c.ndcs.undp.org/soccer-players-and-fans-left-perplexed-after-ball-crosses-the-line-but-no-goal-is-awarded/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
